Your cart is empty
------------------

Your cart
---------

Loading...

Estimated total
---------------

$0.00 USD

Taxes, discounts and [shipping](https://www.halfasleepchris.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout.

Check out

BUY 2 tees and get a free Digital Colouring Book!

Welcome to our store

Country/region
--------------

United States | USD $

 Search

Country/region
--------------

United States | USD $

 Search

 Search [Cart](https://www.halfasleepchris.com/cart)

Privacy policy
==============

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**SECTION 1 - WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT**

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, email address, and/or phone number.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer's internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

**SECTION 2 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

The personal information we collect is stored and processed by us primarily in the United States of America, regardless of your country of residence. We also use affiliated and third party service providers, including hosting and technology partners, who may store and process personal information in other jurisdictions. 

The personal information may be used internally, separately or in combination with information we have collected from other sources, for the following purposes: provide requested services; troubleshoot problems; customize user experience; analyze and improve use of the Site; and compliance with this Policy. With your permission, we may also collect certain personal information so that we may send you emails and SMS messaging about our store, new products and other updates. If you do not wish to receive further communications from us, you may unsubscribe or ask us not to contact you (see "How do I withdraw my consent?" below).

**SECTION 3 - CONSENT**

**_How do you get my consent?_**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

**_How do I withdraw my consent?_**

**_If you are a resident of California or any other state or jurisdiction with privacy protection laws: You have the right to access the Personal Information we have about you (called the "Right to Know" under the California Consumer Privacy Act), to transfer it to a new service, and/or to ask that it be corrected, updated, or erased. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the applicable privacy legislation, nor will we deny you access to our Site, or provide you with a lower quality of services._** 

If you (i) would like to make these requests or designate an authorized agent to make such requests on your behalf, (ii) have any questions or concerns about the Policy, or (iii) wish to  withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, please contact us at customersupport@warrenjames.org.

**SECTION 4 - DISCLOSURE**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

**SECTION 5 - SHOPIFY**

_Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc_. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify's data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

**_Payment:_**

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify's Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

**SECTION 6 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

_In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us._

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act. Once you leave our store's website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website's Terms of Service.

**_Links:_**

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

**_Google analytics:_**

Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

**SECTION 7 - SECURITY**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**SECTION 8 - COOKIES**

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We've listed them here so that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider's internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional

storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where

**SECTION 9 - SMS PRIVACY PRACTICES**

We value your privacy and the information you consent to share in relation to our SMS marketing service. We use this information to send you text notifications (for your order, including abandoned checkout reminders), text marketing offers, and transactional texts, including requests for reviews from us.

Our website uses cookies to keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, including when you have abandoned your checkout. This information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS.

**SECTION 10 - AGE OF CONSENT**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

**SECTION 11 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

The ability to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, or register a complaint is accessible through the website here. If you are having difficulty accessing these services or simply want more information, contact us at customersupport@warrenjames.org, ATTN: Privacy Compliance.

Subscribe to our emails
-----------------------

Be the first to know about new collections and exclusive offers.

 Email

Main Menu
---------

Support Links
-------------

Payment methods

* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* Meta Pay
* Google Pay
* Mastercard
* PayPal
* Shop Pay
* Venmo
* Visa

© 2024, [Half-Asleep Chris](https://www.halfasleepchris.com/) [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
